Contact

eng_manar_bme@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/manar-elsheref-48980130 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

jQuery

CSS

Web Development

Certifications

Content Marketing Foundations
Graphic Design Careers: First Steps
Introduction to Graphic Design:
Concepts

Graphic Design Foundations: Layout and Composition

Color for Design and Art

Manar Elsheref

Webdeveloper, Graphic Design Specialist (Freelance) Egypt

Summary

Experienced Senior Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry.

Skilled in Search Engine Optimization (SEO), PHP, WordPress, jQuery, and Adobe Photoshop, Aftereffects.

Strong information technology professional with a distnict focused in systems and biomedical engineering from Cairo university- faculty of engineering.

Experience

RoayaMas Senior Web Developer,web admin May 2012 - Present (10 years 6 months)

Freelance

Graphic Design Specialist
October 2019 - Present (3 years 1 month)

GPNet

Senior Web Developer, Web Admin August 2007 - December 2009 (2 years 5 months)

Cairo university- cuhtc Center c# senior instructor
October 2004 - 2007 (3 years)

cuhtc instructor 2003 - 2006 (3 years)

Education

Cairo university- faculty of engineering distnict, systems and biomedical engineering